Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 11 and District 11 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 11 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1119
    - Local 1119 Sam Kushner Outgoing Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Kushner to Tom Clark Regarding Evansville and Red-baiting, 1948; 24.
      - Kushner to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Red-baiting, October 7, 1948; 25.
      - Kushner to Charles Kersten Regarding Red-baiting and Evansville, October 7, 1948; 26.
      - Kushner to Gerald Landis Regarding Red-baiting, October 7, 1948; 27.
      - Kushner to Nixon Regarding Political Action, November 30, 1948; 28.
    - Local 1119 General Incoming Correspondence, 1948-1952 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Julius Emspak to Harry Fried Regarding Elkay Manufacturing Strike, March 21, 1949; 1.
      - Emspak to William Burch Regarding LX Strike, June 15, 1950; 2.
      - Emspak to Michael Novik Regarding Tiffin GE, Red-baiting, and Religion, June 23, 1952; 3.
      - Emspak to Burch Regarding Elkay Strike, August 20, 1952; 4.
      - Emspak to Verda Bennet Regarding National Strike Fund, December 18, 1952; 5.
      - A.M. Kinney to UE Members Regarding International Register and Taft-Hartley, March 12, 1948; 6.
      - James Matles to Bernard McDonough Regarding Finances, March 2, 1949; 7.
      - David Ratner to McDonough Regarding Finances, June 15, 1949; 8.
      - Ratner to Pat Amato Regarding Supplies, March 22, 1951; 9.
      - Ratner to Jack Burch, May 4, 1951; 10.
    - Local 1119 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1947-1952 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - William Burch to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Pasche Airbrush Strike, March 23, 1950; 1.
      - Burch to Julius Emspak Regarding Pasche Airbrush Negotiations, June 13, 1950; 2.
      - Burch to Fitzgerald Regarding Inter-union Rivalry and Expulsions, August 9, 1950; 3.
      - Burch to UE Regarding General Laminated and Officers, October 2, 1950; 4.
      - Burch to David Ratner Regarding Supplies, April 13, 1951; 5.
      - Burch to Emspak Regarding Finances and Unemployment, August 13, 1951; 6.
      - Burch to James Matles Regarding Staff Finances, October 10, 1951; 7.
      - Burch to Lewis King Regarding Local 326 Strike, November 9, 1951; 8.
      - Bernard McDonough to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Local 203, March 5, 1947; 9.
      - McDonough to Department of Labor Regarding Lennox Manufacturing Negotiations, May 21, 1947; 10.
      - McDonough to Secretary of Labor Regarding L'Hommedieu and Sons Negotiations, June 7, 1947; 11.
      - McDonough to Emspak Regarding Political Action, August 21, 1947; 12.
      - McDonough to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, September 18, 1947; 13.
      - McDonough to Harry Truman Regarding Red-baiting, December 18, 1947; 14.
      - McDonough to David Ratner Regarding Finances, June 13, 1949; 15.
      - Michael Novik to Emspak Regarding Catholics, June 3, 1952; 16.
    - Local 1119 Notices of Delinquency/Suspension, July 1952 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Local 1119 Press Releases, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Press Release Regarding Foreign Policy, March 23, 1947; 1.
      - Press Release Regarding Legislation and Communist Party, March 23, 1947; 2.
    - Local 1119 Publications, 1948, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - "Stop Thief" Leaflet Regarding IRC Negotiations and Factionalism, March 12, 1948; 1.
      - Stop The Frame-up Pamphlet Regarding Trials, Elkay MOS Strike, and Teamsters Inter-union Rivalry, 2.
    - Local 1119 Organization, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Sam Kushner to Julius Emspak, April 15, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Ernest DeMaio, April 22, 1946; 2.
      - DeMaio to David Ratner, April 22, 1946; 3.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, April 22, 1946; 4.
    - Local 1119 Elkay Manufacturing Competitors, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - James Matles to Walter Barry, February 18, 1947; 1.
      - Matles to Charles Newell, February 18, 1947; 2.
      - Barry to Matles, February 25, 1947; 3.
      - Walter Mugford to Newell, February 25, 1947; 4.
    - Local 1119 National Transformer Strike, 1945-1947 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Report, February 1947; 1.
      - Leo Turner to Julius Emspak, March 11, 1945; 2.
      - Turner to Emspak, April 8, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Turner, April 10, 1947; 4.
    - Local 1119 Elkay Manufacturing Strike, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Ernest DeMaio to Julius Emspak, March 4, 1952; 1.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, March 4, 1952; 2.
      - Memo, March 1952; 3.
      - Janet Barish to DeMaio, April 18, 1952; 4.
      - DeMaio to Barish, May 7, 1952; 5.
      - DeMaio to James Matles, August 1, 1952; 6.
    - Local 1119 Correspondence and Reports, 1947-1953 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Termination of Strike Notice Regarding Linkman and Co., September 22, 1947; 1.
      - Termination of Strike Notice Regarding Brake Equipment, September 29, 1947; 2.
      - Ernest DeMaio to James Matles Regarding Finances, February 23, 1949; 3.
      - Leo Turner to Julius Emspak Regarding Elkay Manufacturing Lockout, March 16, 1949; 4.
      - Fighting Fund Report, March 8, 1952; 5.
      - Matles to DeMaio Regarding Factionalism, Per Capita and Merger of Locals 1114, 1119, and 1150, February 1953; 6.
  - Local 1120
    - Local 1120 Officers Lists, November 12, 1947-March 9, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Local 1120 Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Robert Peterson Regarding Organization, November 4, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Local 1120 Organization, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Donald Murphy to Julius Emspak, September 19, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Ernest DeMaio, October 1, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, October 23, 1947; 3.
      - DeMaio to Emspak, October 29, 1947; 4.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, November 4, 1947; 5.
      - Emspak to Murphy, November 4, 1947; 6.
      - Leo Turner to Emspak, November 8, 1947; 7.
      - Emspak to Turner, December 1, 1947; 8.
  - Local 1121
    - Local 1121 Officers Lists, November 1941-March 12, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Local 1121 Membership Lists, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Local 1121 Membership Resolution Regarding Factionalism, International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, African-Americans, and Local 1119, August 20, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Local 1121 Membership Minutes, June 17, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Local 1121 Earl McGrew Incoming Correspondence, 1939-1942 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - James Carey to Earl McGrew Regarding United Construction Workers Organizing Committee, November 2, 1939; 1.
      - Carey to McGrew Regarding Local 1110, February 2, 1940; 2.
      - Carey to McGrew Regarding Local 1110, February 8, 1940; 3.
      - Carey to McGrew Regarding Local 1110 and Staff Finances, March 11, 1940; 4.
      - Carey to McGrew Regarding Belmont Organization and Factionalism, April 9, 1940; 5.
      - Carey to McGrew Regarding Belmont Organization, April 23, 1940; 6.
      - Carey to McGrew Regarding Construction Workers, June 11, 1940; 7.
      - Carey to McGrew Regarding Tuthill Pump Organization, October 29, 1940; 8.
      - Carey to McGrew Regarding District Boundaries, November 13, 1940; 9.
      - Carey to McGrew Regarding Chicago Congress of Industrial Organizations and District Boundaries, November 27, 1940; 10.
      - Carey to McGrew Regarding Staff Members, Air King, and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, December 2, 1940; 11.
      - Peg Darin to McGrew Regarding Finances, June 22, 1942; 12.
      - Ernest DeMaio to McGrew Regarding Finances and Factionalism, January 17, 1942; 13.
      - DeMaio to McGrew Regarding Finances and Factionalism, January 19, 1942; 14.
      - DeMaio to McGrew Regarding Finances, March 26, 1942; 15.
      - DeMaio to McGrew Regarding Factionalism, April 2, 1942; 16.
      - Julius Emspak to McGrew Regarding Climax Contract, December 12, 1939; 17.
      - Emspak to McGrew Regarding Finances, Factionalism, and Organization with Financial Statement, January 9, 1940; 18.
      - Emspak to McGrew Regarding Tuthill Pump Organization, Steelworkers Organizing Committee Inter-union Rivalry, and Factionalism, January 26, 1940; 19.
      - Emspak to McGrew Regarding General Television Contract, March 20, 1940; 20.
      - Emspak to McGrew Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, October 30, 1940; 21.
      - Emspak to McGrew, January 13, 1941; 22.
      - Emspak to McGrew Regarding Per Capita and Factionalism with Letter of Introduction, December 31, 1941; 23.
      - Emspak to McGrew Regarding Finances and Factionalism, January 13, 1942; 24.
      - Emspak to McGrew Regarding Finances and Factionalism, January 19, 1942; 25.
      - Emspak to McGrew Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, May 15, 1942; 26.
      - Emspak to McGrew Regarding Finances, September 25, 1942; 27.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to McGrew Regarding Factionalism, November 18, 1941; 28.
      - James Matles to McGrew Regarding Warwick Contract, October 31, 1939; 29.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding Minneapolis Honeywell, February 26, 1940; 30.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, April 6, 1940; 31.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, April 20, 1940; 32.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding Tuthill Pump Organization and Factionalism, October 30, 1940; 33.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding General Television and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, November 6, 1940; 34.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, November 12, 1940; 35.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding Organization and Factionalism, February 20, 1941; 36.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding Factionalism, March 4, 1941; 37.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding Mitchell Organization, Factionalism, and Local 1110, May 26, 1941; 38.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding Contracts, October 1, 1941; 39.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding Chicago Organization and Factionalism, October 23, 1941; 40.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding Warwick Contract, November 5, 1941; 41.
      - Matles to McGrew Regarding Warwick Contract, November 12, 1941; 42.
    - Local 1121 Earl McGrew Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Earl McGrew to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 1121 Organization, December 29, 1937; 1.
      - McGrew to James Carey Regarding United Construction Workers Organizing Committee and Organization, November 18, 1939; 2.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding Climax Contracts, Local 1113, and Line Material Negotiations, December 30, 1939; 3.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding Finances, Local 1110, and Tuthill Pump Organization, December 28, 1939; 4.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Bonding, January 8, 1940; 5.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, Tuthill Pump Organization, and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, January 16, 1940; 6.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Staff Members, Factionalism, and Locals 1110 and 1113, January 18, 1940; 7.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Local 1110 and Factionalism, February 5, 1940; 8.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Factionalism, Local 1110, and Staff Finances, February 18, 1940; 9.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Local 1110, Factionalism, and District 11, February 20, 1940; 10.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Local 1110, Factionalism, District 11, and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, February 23, 1940; 11.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Local 1110 and Factionalism, March 1, 1940; 12.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Local 1110 and Factionalism, March 7, 1940; 13.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding General Television Contract, March 15, 1940; 14.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Per Capita, Factionalism, Local 1110, and Staff Members, March 19, 1940; 15.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Belmont Organization, IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, and Staff Members, March 26, 1940; 16.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Belmont Organization and Factionalism, April 2, 1940; 17.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Belmont Organization and Factionalism, April 21, 1940; 18.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Factionalism, Local 1109, Staff Members, Negotiations, and United Construction Workers Organizing Committee with Newspaper Clipping, May 24, 1940; 19.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Tuthill Pump Organization and Staff Members, October 12, 1940; 20.
      - McGrew to James Matles Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry and General Television and Radio Lockout, October 24, 1940; 21.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry and General Television and Radio, October 27, 1940; 22.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry and General Television and Radio, November 5, 1940; 23.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding General Television and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, November 7, 1940; 24.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, General Television, Staff Members, District Boundaries, and Factionalism with Leaflet, November 9, 1940; 25.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Staff Members, November 28, 1940; 26.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Staff Members, December 7, 1940; 27.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding General Television and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, December 28, 1940; 28.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry and General Television, January 4, 1941; 29.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 6, 1941; 30.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding General Television and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry with January 8, 13, and 18, 1941, McGrew Letters to Herman Rose and December 19, 1940, McGrew Letter to James Clark, January 18, 1941; 31.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry and General Television, January 24, 1941; 32.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding General Television, January 25, 1941; 33.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry and General Television Negotiations, February 16, 1941; 34.
      - McGrew to Friend Regarding Radio Products Corporation Organization, February 1941; 35.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding Mitchell Manufacturing Organization, IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, and Factionalism, March 2, 1941; 36.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Organization, March 19, 1941; 37.
      - McGrew to Carey Regarding Finances, Organization, and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, March 20, 1941; 38.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding Mitchell Manufacturing Organization, Factionalism, and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, April 15, 1941; 39.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding Mitchell Manufacturing Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, April 23, 1941; 40.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding Mitchell Manufacturing Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, May 1941; 41.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding Mitchell Manufacturing, May 10, 1941; 42.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding Mitchell Manufacturing, Factionalism, Negotiations, and Organization, May 19, 1941; 43.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding Mitchell Manufacturing Contract and Wages, August 10, 1941; 44.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding Dues, August 25, 1941; 45.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding UE News, Negotiations, and Warwick Contract, October 5, 1941; 46.
      - McGrew to UE Regarding Sonora Organization, October 1941; 47.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding Wages, Warwick Organization, United Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, Company Union, and Factionalism, October 18, 1941; 48.
      - McGrew to Matles Regarding Warwick and General Television Contracts and Erla Organization, November 8, 1941; 49.
      - McGrew to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, November 18, 1941; 50.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, January 1941; 51.
      - McGrew to Lewis Schwellenbach Regarding Mitchell Negotiations, January 20, 1947; 52.
    - Local 1121 General Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1949 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Ernest DeMaio to Local 1121 Members Regarding Factionalism and Officers, February 28, 1947; 1.
      - DeMaio to Ruth Callister Regarding Finances and Factionalism, June 14, 1949; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to John Bisk Regarding Per Capita, June 18, 1937; 3.
      - Emspak to George Deklyne Regarding Finances, July 26, 1937; 4.
      - Emspak to Al Fineman Regarding 1937 UE Convention, August 30, 1937; 5.
      - Emspak to Ralph Friedman Regarding Dues, Organization, and Unemployment, March 26, 1938; 6.
      - Emspak to Norma Jorgenson Regarding Finances, June 14, 1938; 7.
      - Emspak to Jorgenson Regarding Unemployment and Dues, December 27, 1938; 8.
      - Emspak to Harry Kurshenbaum Regarding Organization, Factionalism, and Steelworkers Organizing Committee Inter-union Rivalry, January 26, 1940; 9.
      - Emspak to Vincent Holtman Regarding Sears and Air King Organization, November 27, 1940; 10.
      - Emspak to Kurshenbaum Regarding Finances and Factionalism, January 13, 1942; 11.
      - Emspak to Local 1121 Executive Board Regarding Finances and Factionalism, January 28, 1942; 12.
      - Emspak to Local 1121 Executive Board Regarding Finances, February 3, 1942; 13-15.
      - Emspak to Local 1121 Executive Board Regarding Finances, February 5, 1942; 16.
      - Emspak to Local 1121 Members Regarding Factionalism, June 6, 1942; 17.
      - Emspak to Pat Rogers Regarding Dues and Veterans, August 2, 1945; 18.
      - Emspak to Sidney Loeb Regarding Per Capita, August 11, 1947; 19.
      - Emspak to Ruth Callister Regarding Factionalism, July 1, 1949; 20.
      - Emspak to Fineman Regarding Factionalism, July 21, 1949; 21.
      - Emspak to Callister Regarding Factionalism and Suspension, August 16, 1949; 22.
      - Emspak to Fineman Regarding Motorola Organization, January 6, 1948; 23.
      - H.E. Howard to Kurshenbaum Regarding Staff Members, February 6, 1940; 24.
      - James Matles to Jorgenson Regarding Warwick and Climax, December 19, 1939; 25.
      - David Ratner to Callister Regarding Finances and Factionalism, March 14, 1949; 26.
      - Leo Turner to Ann Carlson Regarding Per Capita and Factionalism, August 3, 1949; 27.
    - Local 1121 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1936-1949 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Victoria Berek to James Carey Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, September 26, 1939; 1.
      - Joseph Cacciatore to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Factionalism, February 1, 1949; 2.
      - Ruth Callister to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, March 16, 1949; 3.
      - Callister to UE News Regarding Factionalism and UE News, July 2, 1949; 4.
      - Al Fineman to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, July 18, 1936; 5.
      - Fineman to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, June 14, 1937; 6.
      - Fineman to Emspak Regarding 1937 UE Convention, August 26, 1937; 7.
      - Fineman to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund and Mitchell Manufacturing Strike, March 26, 1946; 8.
      - Fineman to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Motorola Organization and Factionalism, December 11, 1947; 9.
      - Fineman to Emspak Regarding General Television Bankruptcy, July 20, 1948; 10.
      - Fineman to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, August 23, 1948; 11.
      - Fineman to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Mitchell Negotiations, Factionalism, and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, August 23, 1948; 12.
      - Fineman to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, July 9, 1949; 13.
      - Ralph Friedman to Emspak Regarding Organization, Dues, and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, March 21, 1938; 14.
      - Friedman to Emspak Regarding Philco Boycotts, August 11, 1938; 15.
      - Vincent Hultman to UE News Regarding Sears Union Shops, October 21, 1940; 16.
      - Harry Kurshenbaum Regarding Finances, April 26, 1939; 17.
      - Kurshenbaum to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, Organization, and SWOC Inter-union Rivalry, January 22, 1940; 18.
      - Kurshenbaum to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, January 23, 1942; 19.
      - B.E. Martin to Emspak Regarding 1938 UE Convention, August 5, 1938; 20.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 3, 1939; 21.
      - Eve Mora to James Matles Regarding Factionalism, August 15, 1941; 22.
      - Pat Rogers to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Factionalism, April 7, 1942; 23.
      - Rogers to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, May 4, 1942; 24.
      - Rogers to Emspak Regarding Officers, August 22, 1944; 25.
      - Rogers to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, July 28, 1945; 26.
      - Rogers to Emspak Regarding 1946 UE Convention, August 17, 1946; 27.
      - Sam Sigman to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Warwick, July 9, 1949; 28.
      - Executive Board to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 3, 1942; 29.
      - Recording Secretary to DeMaio Regarding Factionalism, April 15, 1942; 30.
    - Local 1121 Notices of Delinquency/Suspension, November 1937-May 1938 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Local 1121 Report of Financial Secretary, June 1937-August 1938 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Local 1121 Financial Audit, February 1942 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Local 1121 Leaflets, 1940-1949, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - "UERMWA Democracy" Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, October 26, 1940; 1.
      - "Dear Friends" Regarding Sonora Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, January 20, 1941; 2.
      - "Who Was" Regarding Sonora Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, February 6, 1941; 3.
      - "Since The Time" Regarding Mitchell and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, February 26, 1941; 4.
      - "We Wish" Regarding Mitchell and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, February 26, 1941; 5.
      - "CIO Meeting Today" Regarding Mitchell and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, March 18, 1941; 6.
      - "IBEW Stalls" Regarding Mitchell, 1941; 7.
      - "Labor UN Parade for Victory", June 1942; 8.
      - "Mitchell Workers Are Jerks" Regarding Factionalism, April 1949; 9.
      - "Fishing in Muddy Waters" Regarding Mitchell, IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, and Factionalism, June 21, 1949; 10.
      - "Authorization Card" Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, n.d.; 11.
      - "Authoriziation Card", n.d.; 12.
      - "Authorization Card" Regarding Mitchell and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 13.
      - "Authorization Card" Regarding Sonora and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 14.
      - "Authorization Card" Regarding Electrical Research Laboratories, n.d.; 15.
      - "Support The Following" Regarding Factionalism and Officers, 16.
      - "CIO For Mitchell Worker" Regarding Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 17.
      - "Sonora Next" Regarding Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 18.
      - "Chicago Radio Coil Workers" Regarding Organization, n.d.; 19.
      - "To The Chicago Radio Worker" Regarding Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 20.
      - "Marquis in Trouble" Regarding Sonora and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 21.
      - "As A Result" Regarding Sonora and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 22.
      - "Mitchell UE Local 1121 Members" Regarding Wages and Factionalism, 23.
      - "Facts" Regarding Factionalism, n.d.; 24.
    - Local 1121 Newspaper Clippings, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - "Textile Unions See Peaceful Pay Talks", February 9, 1947; 1.
      - "CIO Union Bars Red", February 26, 1947; 2.
      - "Union Charges Leftist Plot", February 27, 1947; 3.
      - "Charges Reds Tie Union in Bonds of Party", February 28, 1947; 4.
      - "Reds Defeated in Election", March 2, 1947; 5.
      - "Anti-Red Re-elected", March 2, 1947; 6.
    - Local 1121 Press Release Regarding Factionalism, Officers, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, and African-Americans, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Local 1121 Publication, 1121 News, November 1948 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Local 1121 Factionalism and Finances, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Ernest DeMaio to James Matles, October 2, 1941; 1.
      - Buford Eastman to Julius Emspak, October 15, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Eastman, October 22, 1951; 3.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, October 31, 1941; 4.